

Profile

I'm a full stack developer with the goal of making the world a little better. I look forward to sharing my knowledge and learning new skills and ideas.

Disclaimer

Some information has been removed from this particular online version. Please send me an email to request the full ${\sf CV}$

Employment History

Full Stack Developer, CSAM, Solna

AUGUST 2021 - PRESENT

Clustered system development for hospitals of different countries

Software Developer, Reynolds Packaging, Green Bay

MAY 2020 - DECEMBER 2020

Development of software in Java and C for data logging and monitoring of industrial machines.

Hemtjänst, Väddö Vård, Älmsta

JUNE 2017 - AUGUST 2019

Summer position in home care services

Education

Computer Science, University of Wisconsin - Green Bay, Green Bay

SEPTEMBER 2017 - MAY 2021

GPA: 3.73 / 4.00

Major Computer Science - Minor Mathematics

Courses

Software Engineering, University of Wisconsin - Green Bay

Artificial Intelligence, University of Wisconsin - Green Bay

Theory of Algorithms, University of Wisconsin - Green Bay

Complete transcript available upon request

References

References available upon request

Details

vicfor002@gmail.com

DRIVING LICENSE

AM/B

DATE OF BIRTH

1996-11-22

Links

Website

Linkedin

GitHub

Skills

Scala

Angular

Cassandra

Java

Docker

GO

C#

Python

SQL

Linux

Languages

Swedish

English

German